<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>CozyDev</title>
    <link>https://chang-wen-chen.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on CozyDev</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>zh-tw</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://chang-wen-chen.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>allegation | accusation</title>
      <link>https://chang-wen-chen.github.io/thesaurus/allegation_accusation/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://chang-wen-chen.github.io/thesaurus/allegation_accusation/</guid>
      <description>Strength of Claim An allegation is a weaker claim than an accusation. It&amp;rsquo;s a statement that someone did something wrong, but there&amp;rsquo;s no guarantee it&amp;rsquo;s true. An accusation is a stronger claim, implying a belief that the wrongdoing is true.&#xA;Evidence Allegations don&amp;rsquo;t necessarily require evidence, while accusations often do. Someone might make an allegation based on suspicion or hearsay, but an accusation usually comes with some kind of proof.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>sarcasm | satire</title>
      <link>https://chang-wen-chen.github.io/thesaurus/sarcasm_satire/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://chang-wen-chen.github.io/thesaurus/sarcasm_satire/</guid>
      <description>Target Sarcasm is a direct attack, often aimed at a specific person or situation. It uses mockery to belittle or criticize. Satire, on the other hand, is broader. It uses humor and exaggeration to comment on social, political, or cultural issues.&#xA;Length Sarcasm is usually delivered in a short jab, like a sarcastic remark. Satire is a more developed critique, often taking the form of a story, essay, cartoon, or even a whole play or film.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>succint | concise</title>
      <link>https://chang-wen-chen.github.io/thesaurus/succint_concise/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://chang-wen-chen.github.io/thesaurus/succint_concise/</guid>
      <description>Concise This emphasizes getting straight to the point and avoiding unnecessary words. It focuses on delivering the essential information clearly and efficiently.&#xA;Succinct This emphasizes using the absolute minimum number of words possible while still being clear. It suggests an even greater level of brevity than concise, almost to the point of being pithy.&#xA;Analogy Think of concise as a well-edited essay that removes fluff and focuses on the main points.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>hesitate | balk</title>
      <link>https://chang-wen-chen.github.io/thesaurus/hesitate_balk/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://chang-wen-chen.github.io/thesaurus/hesitate_balk/</guid>
      <description>Hesitate A more general term for pausing or having doubts before acting. It suggests a moment of indecision, weighing the pros and cons.&#xA;&amp;ldquo;I hesitated before answering the difficult question.&amp;rdquo; Balk A stronger reluctance or even refusal to move forward. It can suggest a sudden stop or resistance due to fear, disapproval, or surprise.&#xA;&amp;ldquo;The horse balked at the jump, refusing to go over.&amp;rdquo; Analogy Hesitation is like a yellow traffic light - you slow down and consider, but might still proceed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>prediction | prophecy</title>
      <link>https://chang-wen-chen.github.io/thesaurus/prediction_prophecy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://chang-wen-chen.github.io/thesaurus/prediction_prophecy/</guid>
      <description>Source Prediction: Based on evidence, logic, or analysis of data. Think weather forecasts or stock market trends. Prophecy: Claimed to come from divine inspiration or supernatural insight. It&amp;rsquo;s often associated with religious figures or texts. Certainty Prediction: Usually presented with probabilities or ranges of possibilities. &amp;ldquo;There&amp;rsquo;s a 70% chance of rain tomorrow.&amp;rdquo; Prophecy: Often portrayed as pronouncements that will definitely come true. &amp;ldquo;The chosen one will bring peace to the land.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>hate | detest | loathe</title>
      <link>https://chang-wen-chen.github.io/thesaurus/hate_detest_loathe/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://chang-wen-chen.github.io/thesaurus/hate_detest_loathe/</guid>
      <description>Hate This is the strongest word of the three. It conveys a deep-seated emotional aversion, often accompanied by anger, hostility, or even disgust. You might hate someone who has wronged you terribly, or a particular activity you find unbearable.&#xA;Detest This word suggests a strong dislike based on disapproval or moral objection. You might detest someone&amp;rsquo;s cruel behavior or a practice you find unethical. It&amp;rsquo;s less emotionally charged than hate.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>arrest | apprehend</title>
      <link>https://chang-wen-chen.github.io/thesaurus/arrest_apprehend/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://chang-wen-chen.github.io/thesaurus/arrest_apprehend/</guid>
      <description>Legality Arrest is a legal term with specific procedures. It usually requires probable cause to believe a crime has been committed. Apprehend is a broader term that can refer to taking someone into custody for any reason, not necessarily criminal.&#xA;Formality Arrest is a formal process with specific rights for the person being arrested. Apprehension can be more informal, like stopping someone suspected of shoplifting.&#xA;Context Arrest is most commonly used in law enforcement situations.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>dominant | predominant</title>
      <link>https://chang-wen-chen.github.io/thesaurus/dominant_predominant/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://chang-wen-chen.github.io/thesaurus/dominant_predominant/</guid>
      <description>Dominant Emphasizes control or power. It suggests that something is clearly the strongest or most important element. For example, a dominant personality is one that tends to take charge and control situations. Or, a dominant force in the market is a company that has a much larger share than its competitors.&#xA;Predominant Emphasizes prevalence or quantity. It suggests that something is the most frequent or common, but it doesn&amp;rsquo;t necessarily imply control.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>drunk | intoxicated</title>
      <link>https://chang-wen-chen.github.io/thesaurus/drunk_intoxicated/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://chang-wen-chen.github.io/thesaurus/drunk_intoxicated/</guid>
      <description>Both &amp;ldquo;drunk&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;intoxicated&amp;rdquo; describe a state caused by consuming alcohol or other substances that impair your body and mind.&#xA;Level of intoxication &amp;ldquo;Drunk&amp;rdquo; often implies a more severe state of intoxication.&#xA;Someone who is drunk might have slurred speech, stumble while walking, or have difficulty thinking clearly.&#xA;Informal vs. formal &amp;ldquo;Drunk&amp;rdquo; is a more informal term, commonly used in everyday conversation.&#xA;&amp;ldquo;Intoxicated&amp;rdquo; has a more formal tone and might be used in legal contexts or medical reports.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>officiate | host</title>
      <link>https://chang-wen-chen.github.io/thesaurus/officiate_host/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://chang-wen-chen.github.io/thesaurus/officiate_host/</guid>
      <description>Officiate: Focuses on presiding over a formal ceremony or ritual. Ensures the ceremony follows established procedures and traditions. Often has a specific authority to perform the ceremony, like legal power in a wedding or religious authority in a religious ceremony.&#xA;A judge officiating a wedding, a priest officiating a baptism. Host Focuses on creating a welcoming and enjoyable atmosphere at an event. Manages the flow and logistics of the event, including introductions, announcements, and entertainment.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>scold | blame | admonish | chide</title>
      <link>https://chang-wen-chen.github.io/thesaurus/scold_blame_admonish_chide/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://chang-wen-chen.github.io/thesaurus/scold_blame_admonish_chide/</guid>
      <description>Scold Most intense and informal. Focuses on sharp criticism and often delivered angrily or with frustration.&#xA;Targets a specific behavior or action. Aims to correct the person&amp;rsquo;s behavior in the moment. Can be used for minor or major offenses. &amp;ldquo;I scolded my child for running into the street.&amp;rdquo; (Focuses on immediate correction) Blame Focuses on assigning responsibility for a negative outcome.&#xA;Can be directed towards a person, object, or situation. Often carries a stronger sense of accusation than scolding.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>apparent | obvious</title>
      <link>https://chang-wen-chen.github.io/thesaurus/apparent_obvious/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://chang-wen-chen.github.io/thesaurus/apparent_obvious/</guid>
      <description>Obvious Something obvious is completely clear and leaves no room for doubt. It&amp;rsquo;s a fact that everyone can easily agree on.&#xA;Apparent Something apparent seems clear and easy to understand, but there might be a chance it&amp;rsquo;s not entirely true or accurate. It&amp;rsquo;s based on what we can see on the surface.&#xA;Sentences It&amp;rsquo;s obvious the earth is round. (There&amp;rsquo;s a lot of evidence to support this fact.) There are apparent scratches on the table, but they might just be dirt.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>anatomize | dissect</title>
      <link>https://chang-wen-chen.github.io/thesaurus/anatomize_dissect/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://chang-wen-chen.github.io/thesaurus/anatomize_dissect/</guid>
      <description>Dissect Focuses on the physical act of carefully cutting something apart to examine its internal structure. This is typically done with a scalpel in a biological context, but it can also be used metaphorically for breaking something down into its component parts.&#xA;Anatomize Implies a deeper analysis beyond just the physical separation. It involves examining the structure and relationships between the parts, often with the goal of understanding how something works as a whole.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>contentment | satisfaction</title>
      <link>https://chang-wen-chen.github.io/thesaurus/contentment_satisfaction/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://chang-wen-chen.github.io/thesaurus/contentment_satisfaction/</guid>
      <description>Satisfaction Often tied to a specific need or desire being fulfilled. You might feel satisfied after eating a delicious meal because your hunger is gone. It&amp;rsquo;s a feeling of completion and accomplishment.&#xA;Contentment More general feeling of peace and acceptance with your current situation. You&amp;rsquo;re happy with things as they are, even if you&amp;rsquo;re not actively pursuing anything new.&#xA;Analogy Imagine a delicious cake. If you eat a slice and feel happy and full, you&amp;rsquo;re satisfied.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>taint | pollute</title>
      <link>https://chang-wen-chen.github.io/thesaurus/taint_pollute/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://chang-wen-chen.github.io/thesaurus/taint_pollute/</guid>
      <description>Taint Taint emphasizes the loss of purity or cleanliness. It suggests something that was once good or innocent has been spoiled or corrupted, even by a small amount of contamination.&#xA;This can be literal, like tainted meat with bacteria, or metaphorical, like a reputation tainted by scandal.&#xA;Pollute Pollute implies a more complete and severe contamination. It often refers to the introduction of harmful or poisonous substances that make something unfit for its original purpose.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>course | trajectory</title>
      <link>https://chang-wen-chen.github.io/thesaurus/course_trajectory/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://chang-wen-chen.github.io/thesaurus/course_trajectory/</guid>
      <description>Course Planned Path: A course is a predetermined path or route that something is intended to follow. It&amp;rsquo;s often used in contexts where there&amp;rsquo;s a deliberate plan or direction. Examples:&#xA;The pilot plotted a course to avoid the storm. (Predetermined flight path) I&amp;#39;m taking a cooking course to learn new recipes. (Planned series of lessons) The river&amp;#39;s course winds through the valley. (Established pathway) Trajectory Actual Path: A trajectory is the actual path something follows as it moves, regardless of intention.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>unpleasant | unsavory</title>
      <link>https://chang-wen-chen.github.io/thesaurus/unpleasant_unsavory/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://chang-wen-chen.github.io/thesaurus/unpleasant_unsavory/</guid>
      <description>Both &amp;ldquo;unpleasant&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;unsavoury&amp;rdquo; describe something negative, but they have some subtle differences:&#xA;Unpleasant: This is a general term for something that is disagreeable, annoying, or uncomfortable. It can refer to anything from a bad smell to a rude person. Unsavoury: This word is stronger than unpleasant and suggests something morally reprehensible, disgusting, or suggestive of corruption. It often implies something that is offensive or upsetting on a deeper level. Illustrate the difference:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stocks | Equities</title>
      <link>https://chang-wen-chen.github.io/fin/stock_equity/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://chang-wen-chen.github.io/fin/stock_equity/</guid>
      <description>Ownership Representation: Stock: Stock represents ownership in a specific company. When you buy stock in a company, you become a shareholder, which means you own a portion of that company. Example: If you purchase 100 shares of Apple stock (AAPL), you own a small portion of Apple Inc. Equity: Equity refers to the ownership interest in a company&amp;rsquo;s assets after deducting liabilities. It represents the residual value available to shareholders after all debts have been paid.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Security DMP</title>
      <link>https://chang-wen-chen.github.io/hardware/dft_security/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://chang-wen-chen.github.io/hardware/dft_security/</guid>
      <description>DMP (Design for Manufacturing and Testability) techniques and methodologies aimed at enhancing the testability and manufacturability of integrated circuits. Security DMP Incorporates security considerations into the design process to ensure that the manufactured chips are resistant to various forms of attacks and unauthorized access.&#xA;Key aspects of security DMP: Secure Test Access Mechanisms Ensures only authorized entities can access the test features of the chip. Secure mechanisms invoke: Implementing authentication Encryption mechanisms Tamper Resistance Protect against physical attacks: probing or tampering with the chip during testing or operation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ultimate Frisbee</title>
      <link>https://chang-wen-chen.github.io/life/ultimate_frisbee/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://chang-wen-chen.github.io/life/ultimate_frisbee/</guid>
      <description>Also call as Ultimate&#xA;History </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The seven wonders</title>
      <link>https://chang-wen-chen.github.io/life/seven_wonders/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://chang-wen-chen.github.io/life/seven_wonders/</guid>
      <description>There are actually two famous lists you might be referring to:&#xA;The Seven Wonders of the Ancient World The New Seven Wonders of the World. The Seven Wonders of the Ancient World were incredible structures built thousands of years ago, but only one remains standing today.&#xA;The Great Pyramid of Giza (the only one still standing)&#xA;The New Seven Wonders of the World, on the other hand, were chosen by a global vote in 2007.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quantum dot</title>
      <link>https://chang-wen-chen.github.io/tech/quantum_dot/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://chang-wen-chen.github.io/tech/quantum_dot/</guid>
      <description>量子點 (quantum dot) 量子點 (quantum dot)是奈米級半導體顆粒，由於其尺寸和成分而表現出獨特的光學和電子特性。 它們通常是由半導體材料製成的微小晶體，例如： 硒化</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>git rerere</title>
      <link>https://chang-wen-chen.github.io/software/scm_git_rerere/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://chang-wen-chen.github.io/software/scm_git_rerere/</guid>
      <description>git rerere 是 Git 中的一個功能，全名是 &amp;ldquo;reuse recorded resolution&amp;rdquo; 意思是重複使用已記錄的解決方案。當你在合併分支或應用補丁時，常常會遇到需要手動解決的衝突情況。但是如果你在</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>git stash</title>
      <link>https://chang-wen-chen.github.io/software/scm_git_stash/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://chang-wen-chen.github.io/software/scm_git_stash/</guid>
      <description>在開發軟體時，可能會遇到一種情境：當某個系統開發已經進行到一半，突然被老闆或客戶「插隊」，需要緊急修正一個現有系統的 Bug 或添加一個功能。 這時候</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>store | stash</title>
      <link>https://chang-wen-chen.github.io/thesaurus/store_stash/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://chang-wen-chen.github.io/thesaurus/store_stash/</guid>
      <description>Store 和 stash 都有存放的意思 Store 通常指將物品放置在一個地方以供未來使用或保管。這個詞通常用於描述將物品儲存在特定的地方或容器中，以便日後取用。 &amp;ldquo;I need to store</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Power Optimization Techniques</title>
      <link>https://chang-wen-chen.github.io/hardware/power_opt/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://chang-wen-chen.github.io/hardware/power_opt/</guid>
      <description>Techniques to optimize design power Clock tree optimization and clock gating Portions of the clock tree(s) that aren’t being used at any particular time are disabled. Operand isolation Reduce power dissipation in datapath blocks controlled by an enable signal; when the datapath element is not active, prevent it from switching.&#xA;Logic restructuring Move high switching operations up in the logic cone, and low switching operations back in the logic cone; a gate-level dynamic power optimization technique.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Data Structure</title>
      <link>https://chang-wen-chen.github.io/software/data_structures/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://chang-wen-chen.github.io/software/data_structures/</guid>
      <description>Linked List Linked list swap file system read CMD pointer manipulate </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Linux Kernal</title>
      <link>https://chang-wen-chen.github.io/infra/linux_kernal/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://chang-wen-chen.github.io/infra/linux_kernal/</guid>
      <description>What is Linux Kernal The kernal is a program Often with a name like vmlinuz- Loaded a run by a noot loader, like GRUB(linux) GRUB GRUB: Load the Kernal program from disk to memory, and transfer the control to kernal GRUB comes after Power-On-self-Test(POST) The Kernal is an API System calls Virtual file system entries (not really a directory) proc sys debugfs Device files(standard system calls, read, write, open,&amp;hellip;etc) The</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DFT Basics</title>
      <link>https://chang-wen-chen.github.io/hardware/dft_basics/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://chang-wen-chen.github.io/hardware/dft_basics/</guid>
      <description>Wafer level testing (Wafer Sort) Burn_in Testing (elevate voltage and temperature) x-axis (clock period) y-axis (Vdd) Final test(pass/fail) and Bin Sorting Parametric Tests(voltage, temperature and clock) Shmoo plot Wafer Sort | probe test Testing on the wafer (before diced) Check open/short on the pads Measure gate threshold, ploy sheet resistence,&amp;hellip;etc Testing with probe cards cost 50~100k dollar depends on the yield and the cost of the packaging (economic problem) DC</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IEEE P1687 IJTAG</title>
      <link>https://chang-wen-chen.github.io/hardware/dft_ijtag/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://chang-wen-chen.github.io/hardware/dft_ijtag/</guid>
      <description>ICL ICL 檔案代表 Instrument Connectivity Language，用於描述測試儀器與待測晶片之間的連接資訊。 測試儀器的類型和配置 待測晶片的測試引腳 測試儀器與待測晶片之間的連</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Verification | Testing</title>
      <link>https://chang-wen-chen.github.io/hardware/dft_testing_verification/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://chang-wen-chen.github.io/hardware/dft_testing_verification/</guid>
      <description> Verification Testing Verifies correctness of the design Verifies correctness of manufactured hardware Performed by simulation, hardware emulation or formal methods Test generation and test application Performed once prior to manufacturing Test application performed on every manufactured device Reponsible for quality of the design Responsible for quality of devices </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FIR forms: direct | transpose</title>
      <link>https://chang-wen-chen.github.io/hardware/fir/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://chang-wen-chen.github.io/hardware/fir/</guid>
      <description>面積 在面積方面，direct form的結構比較簡單，只需要一個乘法器和一個加法器，因此面積比較小。而transpose form的結構比較複雜</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>attain | achieve | accomplish</title>
      <link>https://chang-wen-chen.github.io/thesaurus/attain_achieve_accomplish/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://chang-wen-chen.github.io/thesaurus/attain_achieve_accomplish/</guid>
      <description>Attain: Attain強調達到某種目標或獲得某種地位、成就，通常帶有一定的努力或困難。 He finally attained a high score in the exam, which had been his dream for many years. 他終於在考試中取得了高分，這</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>imperative | declarative</title>
      <link>https://chang-wen-chen.github.io/software/imperative_declarative/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://chang-wen-chen.github.io/software/imperative_declarative/</guid>
      <description>Imperative HOW you do something Imperative programming is a paradigm describing HOW the program should do something by explicitly specifying each instruction (or statement) step by step, which mutate the program&amp;rsquo;s state. Functional programming 是 Declarative Paradigm 的代表，邏輯為用較為抽象的程式碼，理解程式碼想要達到怎樣的目標，F</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>API models: gRPC | OpenAPI | REST</title>
      <link>https://chang-wen-chen.github.io/software/api_models/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://chang-wen-chen.github.io/software/api_models/</guid>
      <description>gRPC 適合需要高效率、強類型、低延遲的系統，特別適用於微服務架構的內部通訊。 OpenAPI 主要用於定義和文檔化 API，提供簡單的工具來自動化生成代碼和文檔。</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gerrit</title>
      <link>https://chang-wen-chen.github.io/software/scm_gerrit/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://chang-wen-chen.github.io/software/scm_gerrit/</guid>
      <description>Code Owners OWNERS file can sit in every directory layer in the repository</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OCV | AOCV | POCV | LVF</title>
      <link>https://chang-wen-chen.github.io/hardware/timing_ocv/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://chang-wen-chen.github.io/hardware/timing_ocv/</guid>
      <description>OCV（On-Chip Variation）： OCV 是指在晶片上的元件之間存在的製造變異。這種變異可能來自於製造過程中的不確定性，例如晶圓製造、成</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>intimidate | threaten</title>
      <link>https://chang-wen-chen.github.io/thesaurus/intimidate_threaten/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://chang-wen-chen.github.io/thesaurus/intimidate_threaten/</guid>
      <description>Intimidate: He tried to intimidate his opponents with his imposing size and aggressive demeanor. 他試圖以他高大威猛的形象和積極的態度來威嚇對手。 Intimidate 通常指的是以某種方式使他人感到害怕或不安，可能是因為某人的外表</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>lewd | obscene | lustful | lascivious</title>
      <link>https://chang-wen-chen.github.io/thesaurus/lewd_obscene_lustful_lascivious/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://chang-wen-chen.github.io/thesaurus/lewd_obscene_lustful_lascivious/</guid>
      <description>這四個詞都是描述不雅或淫蕩的行為或內容 Lewd (不雅): 指的是那些涉及到性的、不雅的、不端的行為或內容。它可能包括性暗示、性行為的描寫或其他被認為</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ostracize | sideline | marginalize</title>
      <link>https://chang-wen-chen.github.io/thesaurus/ostracize_sideline_marginalize/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://chang-wen-chen.github.io/thesaurus/ostracize_sideline_marginalize/</guid>
      <description>Ostracize： 排斥或排擠某人，通常是因為他們的行為或觀點不受歡迎。這種排斥可能是由群體共識或壓力所引起的。 After he spoke out against the company&amp;rsquo;s unethical practices, he was ostracized by his</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>pertain | regards</title>
      <link>https://chang-wen-chen.github.io/thesaurus/pertain_regards/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://chang-wen-chen.github.io/thesaurus/pertain_regards/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Pertain&amp;rdquo; 和 &amp;ldquo;regards&amp;rdquo; 都是英文中用來表達關係或者涉及到的概念，但它們的用法和意義有所不同。 Pertain: 指某事物與某情況有關聯或相關。 The discussion pertains to the recent changes in company policy. (這次討論涉及</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>revenge | retaliation</title>
      <link>https://chang-wen-chen.github.io/thesaurus/revenge_retaliation/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://chang-wen-chen.github.io/thesaurus/revenge_retaliation/</guid>
      <description>Revenge 和 retaliation 都是指對某人或某事的報復行為，但它們之間有些微的差異： Revenge 更偏向於個人情感上的報復，通常是因為受到傷害或冒犯而尋求回應，往往是出於個人的</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shell Display Forwarding</title>
      <link>https://chang-wen-chen.github.io/infra/display_forwarding/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://chang-wen-chen.github.io/infra/display_forwarding/</guid>
      <description>在Shell環境中，DISPLAY環境變數用於指定X Server的位置，以便圖形應用程序知道在哪裡顯示它們的視窗。通常，DISPLAY環境變</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>stigmatize | insult</title>
      <link>https://chang-wen-chen.github.io/thesaurus/stigmatize_insult/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://chang-wen-chen.github.io/thesaurus/stigmatize_insult/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Stigmatize&amp;rdquo; 和 &amp;ldquo;insult&amp;rdquo; 都是描述貶低或貶損某人或某事物的行為 Stigmatize (污名化): 指的是對某人或某群體加諸不公平的社會標籤，通常因為他們的特定特徵、行為或身份而導致被</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>underpin | consolidate</title>
      <link>https://chang-wen-chen.github.io/thesaurus/underpin_consolidate/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://chang-wen-chen.github.io/thesaurus/underpin_consolidate/</guid>
      <description>Underpin 通常指提供支撐或支持，以確保某事物的穩固或穩定。這可以是指物理上的支撐，也可以是指提供基礎或支持性質的抽象概念。例如： The study aims to underpin the theory with empirical evidence.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>utter | say | convey | speak</title>
      <link>https://chang-wen-chen.github.io/thesaurus/utter_say_convey_speak/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://chang-wen-chen.github.io/thesaurus/utter_say_convey_speak/</guid>
      <description>TL;DR utter強調的是發出聲音或言語的行動 say則是用來表達一個具體的言論或意見 convey則指以各種方式傳達信息或感情 speak則是用來描述</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Coffee</title>
      <link>https://chang-wen-chen.github.io/life/coffee/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://chang-wen-chen.github.io/life/coffee/</guid>
      <description>Cold brew 冷萃咖啡 以室溫或冰水萃取的咖啡製作方法，與熱水萃煮的熱咖啡不同，萃取時間更長，通常需要12至24小時的時間。 萃取的過程中，咖啡粉會與水慢</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Investment Terms</title>
      <link>https://chang-wen-chen.github.io/fin/fin_terms/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://chang-wen-chen.github.io/fin/fin_terms/</guid>
      <description>Angel Investment Stream 天使投資流，它是一種投資方式，通常指的是個人投資者或小型投資團體向初創企業提供資金支持的過程。這些投資者被稱為「天使投資者」，因為他們</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SVE | SME</title>
      <link>https://chang-wen-chen.github.io/hardware/isa_sve_sme/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://chang-wen-chen.github.io/hardware/isa_sve_sme/</guid>
      <description>SVE SVE，或可擴充向量擴充（Scalable Vector Extensions），是一種新的指令集架構，專為向量處理設計。向量處理是一種並行處理，可用於</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>.war and .jar in Java</title>
      <link>https://chang-wen-chen.github.io/software/java_war_jar/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://chang-wen-chen.github.io/software/java_war_jar/</guid>
      <description>在Java語言中，.war 和 .jar 是兩種不同的壓縮文件格式，通常用於打包和部署Java應用程序。它們之間的主要區別在於它們的用途和內容： .war (Web Application Archive):</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mobile photography</title>
      <link>https://chang-wen-chen.github.io/life/mobile_photography/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://chang-wen-chen.github.io/life/mobile_photography/</guid>
      <description>設定 照片打開ProRes 手機攝影 三分線構圖法 黃金比例：看了很舒服的構圖 把物體放在左右下角的點上 或是這四個點上/附近 三角構圖 (人像) 勾勒出三角</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Clock Tree Synthesis</title>
      <link>https://chang-wen-chen.github.io/hardware/cts_architecture/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://chang-wen-chen.github.io/hardware/cts_architecture/</guid>
      <description>CTS（Clock Tree Synthesis）、Multisource CTS 和時鐘網格（Clock Mesh）是在Digital IC design中用於時鐘</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Python</title>
      <link>https://chang-wen-chen.github.io/software/python/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://chang-wen-chen.github.io/software/python/</guid>
      <description>Cpython Py_INCREF() and Py_DECREF() While Py_INCREF() and Py_DECREF() are essential components of Python&amp;rsquo;s memory management system, they&amp;rsquo;re not the ideal way to directly count how many times a Python variable is used. Let me explain why and offer better alternatives: Role: These functions are at the heart of Python&amp;rsquo;s reference counting garbage collection. Py_INCREF(object): Increments the reference count of an object. This indicates that the object is in use and</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Real estates</title>
      <link>https://chang-wen-chen.github.io/life/real_estate/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://chang-wen-chen.github.io/life/real_estate/</guid>
      <description>Property tax Mortage loan Contract 不用理會口頭承諾 （Ｘ）貸款貸不到，現金補足，以繳價金沒收 （Ｏ）貸款貸不到，雙方合約無條件解除，以繳價金無條件返還 小心特約條款：「不</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>xPU</title>
      <link>https://chang-wen-chen.github.io/hardware/xpu/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://chang-wen-chen.github.io/hardware/xpu/</guid>
      <description>CPU model and performance Naming cenvention Intel AMD Example Core-i7-10875H Ryzen 7-5800H Series Core-i7 Ryzen 7 Generation 10 5 Performance 875 800 Product line H H Series 對比 Level Intel AMD 入門 Pentium Athlon 低階 Core-i3 Ryzen 3 中階 Core-i5 Ryzen 5 高階 Core-i7 Ryzen 7 旗艦 Core-i9 Ryzen 9 Product line 對比 CPU Benchmark Product line Intel AMD 超低功耗</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DBMS Data Types</title>
      <link>https://chang-wen-chen.github.io/software/dbms_data_types/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://chang-wen-chen.github.io/software/dbms_data_types/</guid>
      <description>結構化數據 (Structured Data): 結構化數據是以固定格式和結構存儲的數據。通常，結構化數據可以使用表格或者數據庫中的行和列來表示。 例子：關係型數據庫中的表格、E</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google cloud storage options</title>
      <link>https://chang-wen-chen.github.io/software/gcloud_storage/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://chang-wen-chen.github.io/software/gcloud_storage/</guid>
      <description>Google cloud provides 5 storage products: Cloud Storage Cloud SQL Cloud Spanner Firestore Cloud Bigtable 1. Cloud storage Google&amp;rsquo;s object storage product. It allows user to store any amount of data and retrieve it as often as needed. Fully managed scalable service that has wide variety of uses. Example: web archival and disaster recovery, website content, direct download. Primary use: Binary large-object storage (BLOB) Online contents: videos and photos Backup and archiving Storage of intermediate results object storage: store data as object but not as file and folder hierarchy(file storage), or as chunks of a disk(block storage)</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>git rebase</title>
      <link>https://chang-wen-chen.github.io/software/scm_git_rebase/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://chang-wen-chen.github.io/software/scm_git_rebase/</guid>
      <description>In your local clone of your forked repository, you can add the original GitHub repository as a &amp;ldquo;remote&amp;rdquo;. (&amp;ldquo;Remotes&amp;rdquo; are like nicknames for the URLs of repositories - origin is one, for example.) Then you can fetch all the branches from that upstream repository, and rebase your work to continue working on the upstream version. 到你 fork repository 的 local cloned area 中，你可以將原</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JPLT skill</title>
      <link>https://chang-wen-chen.github.io/life/jplt_prepare/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://chang-wen-chen.github.io/life/jplt_prepare/</guid>
      <description>N2 在日本求學、工作生活較適合 600-800 hr 學習 目標設定 N4 學習時間 晚上9-11 學習日檢 日文基礎 手寫五十音 手機背誦遊戲 單字：1500 字 文法： 大家的日本語初</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shell commands</title>
      <link>https://chang-wen-chen.github.io/infra/shell/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://chang-wen-chen.github.io/infra/shell/</guid>
      <description>set -euo pipefail 在Shell script中，set -euo pipefail 是設置script的選項，它們影響script的行為。逐個解釋這些選項： -e 這個選項使得scrip</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>conduct | execute</title>
      <link>https://chang-wen-chen.github.io/thesaurus/conduct_execute/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://chang-wen-chen.github.io/thesaurus/conduct_execute/</guid>
      <description>Conduct 意義：「進行」、「執行」、「管理」。 The research team conducted experiments to test their hypothesis. （研究團隊進行實驗來測試他們的假設。） The CEO conducted the meeting to discuss the company&amp;rsquo;s future plans. （CEO主持了會議，討論</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>interium | temporary</title>
      <link>https://chang-wen-chen.github.io/thesaurus/interium_temporary/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://chang-wen-chen.github.io/thesaurus/interium_temporary/</guid>
      <description>Interim 通常指的是在某個時間段或者某個事件之間的暫時性。它可能是在等待更長期或更永久性的解決方案之前的中間期間。這個詞通常用於指派職位或者擔任角色</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>mitigate | alleviate | relieve</title>
      <link>https://chang-wen-chen.github.io/thesaurus/mitigate_alleviate_relieve/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://chang-wen-chen.github.io/thesaurus/mitigate_alleviate_relieve/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Mitigate,&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;alleviate,&amp;rdquo; 和 &amp;ldquo;relieve&amp;rdquo; 這三個詞都意指減輕或解決問題、困難或痛苦，但它們在用法上有些微的差異。 Mitigate：通常指採取行動來減輕或降低某種不利狀況、風險</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>suppose | conjecture</title>
      <link>https://chang-wen-chen.github.io/thesaurus/suppose_conjecture/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://chang-wen-chen.github.io/thesaurus/suppose_conjecture/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Suppose&amp;rdquo; 和 &amp;ldquo;conjecture&amp;rdquo; 都是用來表達假設或猜測的詞語，但它們之間有些微的差異。 &amp;ldquo;Suppose&amp;rdquo; 基於已知或可接受的前提下提出一個假設，通常假設是基於事實或常識的推論。它可能有</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Processes and jobs</title>
      <link>https://chang-wen-chen.github.io/infra/process_job/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://chang-wen-chen.github.io/infra/process_job/</guid>
      <description>In Linux systems, &amp;ldquo;process&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;job&amp;rdquo; are two distinct concepts representing different units of execution. Here&amp;rsquo;s the difference between them along with some common examples: Process: A process is an instance of a program running in the operating system. Each process has its own memory space, code, data, open files, resources, and state. Processes are independent of each other and cannot directly access the memory space of other processes. A</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SSL | TLS | HTTPS</title>
      <link>https://chang-wen-chen.github.io/software/ssl_tls_https/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://chang-wen-chen.github.io/software/ssl_tls_https/</guid>
      <description>Similarities: Security: Both SSL (Secure Sockets Layer) and TLS (Transport Layer Security) are protocols designed to provide secure communication channels over the internet, encrypting data during transmission to prevent interception or eavesdropping by third parties. Encryption Algorithms: SSL and TLS support various encryption algorithms, including symmetric encryption, asymmetric encryption, and digital signature algorithms, to ensure data confidentiality, integrity, and authenticity. Handshake Protocol: SSL and TLS both require a handshake protocol</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Various dbms</title>
      <link>https://chang-wen-chen.github.io/software/dbms/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://chang-wen-chen.github.io/software/dbms/</guid>
      <description>Relational Databases: Structured Data: Data is organized in tables with predefined structures, each table consisting of fixed columns and column types. SQL Query Language: Relational databases typically use SQL (Structured Query Language) for executing queries and managing data. Strong Consistency: They usually provide ACID (Atomicity, Consistency, Isolation, Durability) properties, ensuring data consistency and reliability. Vertical Scaling: They often employ vertical scaling, meaning adding more hardware resources to improve performance. Example</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>appraise | evaluation</title>
      <link>https://chang-wen-chen.github.io/thesaurus/appraise_evaluation/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://chang-wen-chen.github.io/thesaurus/appraise_evaluation/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Evaluate&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;appraise&amp;rdquo; are two terms that involve assessing something, but they have slightly different connotations and applications. Evaluate: This term implies a comprehensive assessment or analysis of something, often with the aim of understanding its worth, quality, effectiveness, or significance. Evaluation typically involves considering various factors, gathering information, and making judgments or conclusions based on criteria. It&amp;rsquo;s a broader term that can be applied in various contexts, such as</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>maintain | uphold</title>
      <link>https://chang-wen-chen.github.io/thesaurus/maintain_uphold/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://chang-wen-chen.github.io/thesaurus/maintain_uphold/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Maintain&amp;rdquo; typically refers to the act of keeping something in a particular state or condition, often through regular efforts or actions. It can imply preserving, supporting, or caring for something over time. &amp;ldquo;Maintain&amp;rdquo; 通常指的是透過定期的努力或行動，將某物保持在特定的狀態或條件中。它可以暗示</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OSI Model</title>
      <link>https://chang-wen-chen.github.io/network/osi_model/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://chang-wen-chen.github.io/network/osi_model/</guid>
      <description>Router 可以處理Layer3 header，可稱為Layer3 Physical Layer: 如何把原始資料在Link 上傳輸，無論有線或無線 Coaxial cable (同軸電纜，外層包覆可降低電磁波</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HTML Basics</title>
      <link>https://chang-wen-chen.github.io/software/html_basics/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://chang-wen-chen.github.io/software/html_basics/</guid>
      <description> All HTML elements can have attributes The href attribute of &amp;lt;a&amp;gt; specifies the URL of the page the link goes to The src attribute of &amp;lt;img&amp;gt; specifies the path to the image to be displayed The width and height attributes of &amp;lt;img&amp;gt; provide size information for images The alt attribute of &amp;lt;img&amp;gt; provides an alternate text for an image The style attribute is used to add styles to an element, such as color, font, size, and more The lang attribute of the &amp;lt;html&amp;gt; tag declares the language of the Web page The title attribute defines some extra information about an element </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mercurial and Git</title>
      <link>https://chang-wen-chen.github.io/software/scm-mercurial-git/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://chang-wen-chen.github.io/software/scm-mercurial-git/</guid>
      <description>Mercurial and Git are both used for version control. Both Mercurial (Hg) and Git are popular distributed version control systems (DVCS), but they have some key differences in their approach: Branching Model: Mercurial: Employs a centralized branching model, meaning each branch has its own separate directory. Switching branches involves changing directories. This can be simpler for beginners but less flexible for complex workflows. Git: Uses a decentralized branching model, where</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Classic cocktail</title>
      <link>https://chang-wen-chen.github.io/life/classic_cocktail/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://chang-wen-chen.github.io/life/classic_cocktail/</guid>
      <description>調酒的基礎是基酒，基酒是指調酒的基底，通常占最大的比例，酒精濃度高，約在40~45%之間，且多為蒸餾酒。 常見的基酒種類如下： 琴酒（Gin）：</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>commitment | promise</title>
      <link>https://chang-wen-chen.github.io/thesaurus/commitment_promise/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://chang-wen-chen.github.io/thesaurus/commitment_promise/</guid>
      <description>A commitment holds more weight than a simple promise Emphasis on intent: Commitment signifies a genuine desire to fulfill the promise, suggesting sincerity and motivation. Focus on strength: Commitment implies a stronger promise than one can readily deliver, highlighting its ambitious nature. Contrast with indulgence: Commitment stands against indulgence, emphasizing dedication and perseverance as key differentiators. In essence, commitments go beyond empty promises, demonstrating a willingness to put in the</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tequila | Mezcal</title>
      <link>https://chang-wen-chen.github.io/life/tequila_mezcal/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://chang-wen-chen.github.io/life/tequila_mezcal/</guid>
      <description>Tequila and Mezcal: What are the differences?&#xA;Tequila and mezcal are both Mexican spirits distilled from the agave plant. However, there are some key differences between them.&#xA;Tequila&#xA;Must be made from 100% blue agave plant. Can only be produced in five Mexican states: Jalisco, Nayarit, Guanajuato, Tamaulipas, and Michoacán. Typically distilled in stainless steel tanks. Usually unaged, but can also be aged in wooden barrels. Mezcal&#xA;Can be made from any type of agave plant, but most commonly espadín agave.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://chang-wen-chen.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://chang-wen-chen.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>About Me Chang Wen Chen is a CAD architecture and chip design engineer, offering 5+ years of experience in both hardware design as well as software development. Products conducted including 5G modern chips, CPU with advance process nodes and automatic CAD flow development.&#xA;Strong skills in back-end implementation, process in advance nodes, timing/power/area/schedule analyzing, flow automation. Excelled at integrating information and communicating.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://chang-wen-chen.github.io/notes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://chang-wen-chen.github.io/notes/</guid>
      <description>GoLang 筆記 Computer Networking 筆記 Google Cloud 筆記</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://chang-wen-chen.github.io/search/placeholder/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://chang-wen-chen.github.io/search/placeholder/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Posts Archive</title>
      <link>https://chang-wen-chen.github.io/archive/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://chang-wen-chen.github.io/archive/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
