<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>DFT on CozyDev</title>
    <link>https://chang-wen-chen.github.io/tags/dft/</link>
    <description>Recent content in DFT on CozyDev</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>zh-tw</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://chang-wen-chen.github.io/tags/dft/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Security DMP</title>
      <link>https://chang-wen-chen.github.io/hardware/dft_security/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://chang-wen-chen.github.io/hardware/dft_security/</guid>
      <description>DMP (Design for Manufacturing and Testability) techniques and methodologies aimed at enhancing the testability and manufacturability of integrated circuits. Security DMP Incorporates security considerations into the design process to ensure that the manufactured chips are resistant to various forms of attacks and unauthorized access.&#xA;Key aspects of security DMP: Secure Test Access Mechanisms Ensures only authorized entities can access the test features of the chip. Secure mechanisms invoke: Implementing authentication Encryption mechanisms Tamper Resistance Protect against physical attacks: probing or tampering with the chip during testing or operation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DFT Basics</title>
      <link>https://chang-wen-chen.github.io/hardware/dft_basics/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://chang-wen-chen.github.io/hardware/dft_basics/</guid>
      <description>Wafer level testing (Wafer Sort) Burn_in Testing (elevate voltage and temperature) x-axis (clock period) y-axis (Vdd) Final test(pass/fail) and Bin Sorting Parametric Tests(voltage, temperature and clock) Shmoo plot Wafer Sort | probe test Testing on the wafer (before diced) Check open/short on the pads Measure gate threshold, ploy sheet resistence,&amp;hellip;etc Testing with probe cards cost 50~100k dollar depends on the yield and the cost of the packaging (economic problem) DC</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IEEE P1687 IJTAG</title>
      <link>https://chang-wen-chen.github.io/hardware/dft_ijtag/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://chang-wen-chen.github.io/hardware/dft_ijtag/</guid>
      <description>ICL ICL 檔案代表 Instrument Connectivity Language，用於描述測試儀器與待測晶片之間的連接資訊。 測試儀器的類型和配置 待測晶片的測試引腳 測試儀器與待測晶片之間的連</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Verification | Testing</title>
      <link>https://chang-wen-chen.github.io/hardware/dft_testing_verification/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://chang-wen-chen.github.io/hardware/dft_testing_verification/</guid>
      <description> Verification Testing Verifies correctness of the design Verifies correctness of manufactured hardware Performed by simulation, hardware emulation or formal methods Test generation and test application Performed once prior to manufacturing Test application performed on every manufactured device Reponsible for quality of the design Responsible for quality of devices </description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
