<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>English on CozyDev</title>
    <link>https://chang-wen-chen.github.io/tags/english/</link>
    <description>Recent content in English on CozyDev</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>zh-tw</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 26 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://chang-wen-chen.github.io/tags/english/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>hate | detest | loathe</title>
      <link>https://chang-wen-chen.github.io/thesaurus/hate_detest_loathe/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://chang-wen-chen.github.io/thesaurus/hate_detest_loathe/</guid>
      <description>Hate This is the strongest word of the three. It conveys a deep-seated emotional aversion, often accompanied by anger, hostility, or even disgust. You might hate someone who has wronged you terribly, or a particular activity you find unbearable.&#xA;Detest This word suggests a strong dislike based on disapproval or moral objection. You might detest someone&amp;rsquo;s cruel behavior or a practice you find unethical. It&amp;rsquo;s less emotionally charged than hate.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>arrest | apprehend</title>
      <link>https://chang-wen-chen.github.io/thesaurus/arrest_apprehend/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://chang-wen-chen.github.io/thesaurus/arrest_apprehend/</guid>
      <description>Legality Arrest is a legal term with specific procedures. It usually requires probable cause to believe a crime has been committed. Apprehend is a broader term that can refer to taking someone into custody for any reason, not necessarily criminal.&#xA;Formality Arrest is a formal process with specific rights for the person being arrested. Apprehension can be more informal, like stopping someone suspected of shoplifting.&#xA;Context Arrest is most commonly used in law enforcement situations.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>dominant | predominant</title>
      <link>https://chang-wen-chen.github.io/thesaurus/dominant_predominant/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://chang-wen-chen.github.io/thesaurus/dominant_predominant/</guid>
      <description>Dominant Emphasizes control or power. It suggests that something is clearly the strongest or most important element. For example, a dominant personality is one that tends to take charge and control situations. Or, a dominant force in the market is a company that has a much larger share than its competitors.&#xA;Predominant Emphasizes prevalence or quantity. It suggests that something is the most frequent or common, but it doesn&amp;rsquo;t necessarily imply control.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>drunk | intoxicated</title>
      <link>https://chang-wen-chen.github.io/thesaurus/drunk_intoxicated/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://chang-wen-chen.github.io/thesaurus/drunk_intoxicated/</guid>
      <description>Both &amp;ldquo;drunk&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;intoxicated&amp;rdquo; describe a state caused by consuming alcohol or other substances that impair your body and mind.&#xA;Level of intoxication &amp;ldquo;Drunk&amp;rdquo; often implies a more severe state of intoxication.&#xA;Someone who is drunk might have slurred speech, stumble while walking, or have difficulty thinking clearly.&#xA;Informal vs. formal &amp;ldquo;Drunk&amp;rdquo; is a more informal term, commonly used in everyday conversation.&#xA;&amp;ldquo;Intoxicated&amp;rdquo; has a more formal tone and might be used in legal contexts or medical reports.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>officiate | host</title>
      <link>https://chang-wen-chen.github.io/thesaurus/officiate_host/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://chang-wen-chen.github.io/thesaurus/officiate_host/</guid>
      <description>Officiate: Focuses on presiding over a formal ceremony or ritual. Ensures the ceremony follows established procedures and traditions. Often has a specific authority to perform the ceremony, like legal power in a wedding or religious authority in a religious ceremony.&#xA;A judge officiating a wedding, a priest officiating a baptism. Host Focuses on creating a welcoming and enjoyable atmosphere at an event. Manages the flow and logistics of the event, including introductions, announcements, and entertainment.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>scold | blame | admonish | chide</title>
      <link>https://chang-wen-chen.github.io/thesaurus/scold_blame_admonish_chide/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://chang-wen-chen.github.io/thesaurus/scold_blame_admonish_chide/</guid>
      <description>Scold Most intense and informal. Focuses on sharp criticism and often delivered angrily or with frustration.&#xA;Targets a specific behavior or action. Aims to correct the person&amp;rsquo;s behavior in the moment. Can be used for minor or major offenses. &amp;ldquo;I scolded my child for running into the street.&amp;rdquo; (Focuses on immediate correction) Blame Focuses on assigning responsibility for a negative outcome.&#xA;Can be directed towards a person, object, or situation. Often carries a stronger sense of accusation than scolding.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>apparent | obvious</title>
      <link>https://chang-wen-chen.github.io/thesaurus/apparent_obvious/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://chang-wen-chen.github.io/thesaurus/apparent_obvious/</guid>
      <description>Obvious Something obvious is completely clear and leaves no room for doubt. It&amp;rsquo;s a fact that everyone can easily agree on.&#xA;Apparent Something apparent seems clear and easy to understand, but there might be a chance it&amp;rsquo;s not entirely true or accurate. It&amp;rsquo;s based on what we can see on the surface.&#xA;Sentences It&amp;rsquo;s obvious the earth is round. (There&amp;rsquo;s a lot of evidence to support this fact.) There are apparent scratches on the table, but they might just be dirt.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>anatomize | dissect</title>
      <link>https://chang-wen-chen.github.io/thesaurus/anatomize_dissect/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://chang-wen-chen.github.io/thesaurus/anatomize_dissect/</guid>
      <description>Dissect Focuses on the physical act of carefully cutting something apart to examine its internal structure. This is typically done with a scalpel in a biological context, but it can also be used metaphorically for breaking something down into its component parts.&#xA;Anatomize Implies a deeper analysis beyond just the physical separation. It involves examining the structure and relationships between the parts, often with the goal of understanding how something works as a whole.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>contentment | satisfaction</title>
      <link>https://chang-wen-chen.github.io/thesaurus/contentment_satisfaction/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://chang-wen-chen.github.io/thesaurus/contentment_satisfaction/</guid>
      <description>Satisfaction Often tied to a specific need or desire being fulfilled. You might feel satisfied after eating a delicious meal because your hunger is gone. It&amp;rsquo;s a feeling of completion and accomplishment.&#xA;Contentment More general feeling of peace and acceptance with your current situation. You&amp;rsquo;re happy with things as they are, even if you&amp;rsquo;re not actively pursuing anything new.&#xA;Analogy Imagine a delicious cake. If you eat a slice and feel happy and full, you&amp;rsquo;re satisfied.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>taint | pollute</title>
      <link>https://chang-wen-chen.github.io/thesaurus/taint_pollute/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://chang-wen-chen.github.io/thesaurus/taint_pollute/</guid>
      <description>Taint Taint emphasizes the loss of purity or cleanliness. It suggests something that was once good or innocent has been spoiled or corrupted, even by a small amount of contamination.&#xA;This can be literal, like tainted meat with bacteria, or metaphorical, like a reputation tainted by scandal.&#xA;Pollute Pollute implies a more complete and severe contamination. It often refers to the introduction of harmful or poisonous substances that make something unfit for its original purpose.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>course | trajectory</title>
      <link>https://chang-wen-chen.github.io/thesaurus/course_trajectory/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://chang-wen-chen.github.io/thesaurus/course_trajectory/</guid>
      <description>Course Planned Path: A course is a predetermined path or route that something is intended to follow. It&amp;rsquo;s often used in contexts where there&amp;rsquo;s a deliberate plan or direction. Examples:&#xA;The pilot plotted a course to avoid the storm. (Predetermined flight path) I&amp;#39;m taking a cooking course to learn new recipes. (Planned series of lessons) The river&amp;#39;s course winds through the valley. (Established pathway) Trajectory Actual Path: A trajectory is the actual path something follows as it moves, regardless of intention.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>unpleasant | unsavory</title>
      <link>https://chang-wen-chen.github.io/thesaurus/unpleasant_unsavory/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://chang-wen-chen.github.io/thesaurus/unpleasant_unsavory/</guid>
      <description>Both &amp;ldquo;unpleasant&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;unsavoury&amp;rdquo; describe something negative, but they have some subtle differences:&#xA;Unpleasant: This is a general term for something that is disagreeable, annoying, or uncomfortable. It can refer to anything from a bad smell to a rude person. Unsavoury: This word is stronger than unpleasant and suggests something morally reprehensible, disgusting, or suggestive of corruption. It often implies something that is offensive or upsetting on a deeper level. Illustrate the difference:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>store | stash</title>
      <link>https://chang-wen-chen.github.io/thesaurus/store_stash/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://chang-wen-chen.github.io/thesaurus/store_stash/</guid>
      <description>Store 和 stash 都有存放的意思 Store 通常指將物品放置在一個地方以供未來使用或保管。這個詞通常用於描述將物品儲存在特定的地方或容器中，以便日後取用。 &amp;ldquo;I need to store</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>attain | achieve | accomplish</title>
      <link>https://chang-wen-chen.github.io/thesaurus/attain_achieve_accomplish/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://chang-wen-chen.github.io/thesaurus/attain_achieve_accomplish/</guid>
      <description>Attain: Attain強調達到某種目標或獲得某種地位、成就，通常帶有一定的努力或困難。 He finally attained a high score in the exam, which had been his dream for many years. 他終於在考試中取得了高分，這</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>intimidate | threaten</title>
      <link>https://chang-wen-chen.github.io/thesaurus/intimidate_threaten/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://chang-wen-chen.github.io/thesaurus/intimidate_threaten/</guid>
      <description>Intimidate: He tried to intimidate his opponents with his imposing size and aggressive demeanor. 他試圖以他高大威猛的形象和積極的態度來威嚇對手。 Intimidate 通常指的是以某種方式使他人感到害怕或不安，可能是因為某人的外表</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>lewd | obscene | lustful | lascivious</title>
      <link>https://chang-wen-chen.github.io/thesaurus/lewd_obscene_lustful_lascivious/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://chang-wen-chen.github.io/thesaurus/lewd_obscene_lustful_lascivious/</guid>
      <description>這四個詞都是描述不雅或淫蕩的行為或內容 Lewd (不雅): 指的是那些涉及到性的、不雅的、不端的行為或內容。它可能包括性暗示、性行為的描寫或其他被認為</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ostracize | sideline | marginalize</title>
      <link>https://chang-wen-chen.github.io/thesaurus/ostracize_sideline_marginalize/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://chang-wen-chen.github.io/thesaurus/ostracize_sideline_marginalize/</guid>
      <description>Ostracize： 排斥或排擠某人，通常是因為他們的行為或觀點不受歡迎。這種排斥可能是由群體共識或壓力所引起的。 After he spoke out against the company&amp;rsquo;s unethical practices, he was ostracized by his</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>pertain | regards</title>
      <link>https://chang-wen-chen.github.io/thesaurus/pertain_regards/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://chang-wen-chen.github.io/thesaurus/pertain_regards/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Pertain&amp;rdquo; 和 &amp;ldquo;regards&amp;rdquo; 都是英文中用來表達關係或者涉及到的概念，但它們的用法和意義有所不同。 Pertain: 指某事物與某情況有關聯或相關。 The discussion pertains to the recent changes in company policy. (這次討論涉及</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>revenge | retaliation</title>
      <link>https://chang-wen-chen.github.io/thesaurus/revenge_retaliation/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://chang-wen-chen.github.io/thesaurus/revenge_retaliation/</guid>
      <description>Revenge 和 retaliation 都是指對某人或某事的報復行為，但它們之間有些微的差異： Revenge 更偏向於個人情感上的報復，通常是因為受到傷害或冒犯而尋求回應，往往是出於個人的</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>stigmatize | insult</title>
      <link>https://chang-wen-chen.github.io/thesaurus/stigmatize_insult/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://chang-wen-chen.github.io/thesaurus/stigmatize_insult/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Stigmatize&amp;rdquo; 和 &amp;ldquo;insult&amp;rdquo; 都是描述貶低或貶損某人或某事物的行為 Stigmatize (污名化): 指的是對某人或某群體加諸不公平的社會標籤，通常因為他們的特定特徵、行為或身份而導致被</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>underpin | consolidate</title>
      <link>https://chang-wen-chen.github.io/thesaurus/underpin_consolidate/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://chang-wen-chen.github.io/thesaurus/underpin_consolidate/</guid>
      <description>Underpin 通常指提供支撐或支持，以確保某事物的穩固或穩定。這可以是指物理上的支撐，也可以是指提供基礎或支持性質的抽象概念。例如： The study aims to underpin the theory with empirical evidence.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>utter | say | convey | speak</title>
      <link>https://chang-wen-chen.github.io/thesaurus/utter_say_convey_speak/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://chang-wen-chen.github.io/thesaurus/utter_say_convey_speak/</guid>
      <description>TL;DR utter強調的是發出聲音或言語的行動 say則是用來表達一個具體的言論或意見 convey則指以各種方式傳達信息或感情 speak則是用來描述</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>conduct | execute</title>
      <link>https://chang-wen-chen.github.io/thesaurus/conduct_execute/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://chang-wen-chen.github.io/thesaurus/conduct_execute/</guid>
      <description>Conduct 意義：「進行」、「執行」、「管理」。 The research team conducted experiments to test their hypothesis. （研究團隊進行實驗來測試他們的假設。） The CEO conducted the meeting to discuss the company&amp;rsquo;s future plans. （CEO主持了會議，討論</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>interium | temporary</title>
      <link>https://chang-wen-chen.github.io/thesaurus/interium_temporary/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://chang-wen-chen.github.io/thesaurus/interium_temporary/</guid>
      <description>Interim 通常指的是在某個時間段或者某個事件之間的暫時性。它可能是在等待更長期或更永久性的解決方案之前的中間期間。這個詞通常用於指派職位或者擔任角色</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>mitigate | alleviate | relieve</title>
      <link>https://chang-wen-chen.github.io/thesaurus/mitigate_alleviate_relieve/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://chang-wen-chen.github.io/thesaurus/mitigate_alleviate_relieve/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Mitigate,&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;alleviate,&amp;rdquo; 和 &amp;ldquo;relieve&amp;rdquo; 這三個詞都意指減輕或解決問題、困難或痛苦，但它們在用法上有些微的差異。 Mitigate：通常指採取行動來減輕或降低某種不利狀況、風險</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>suppose | conjecture</title>
      <link>https://chang-wen-chen.github.io/thesaurus/suppose_conjecture/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://chang-wen-chen.github.io/thesaurus/suppose_conjecture/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Suppose&amp;rdquo; 和 &amp;ldquo;conjecture&amp;rdquo; 都是用來表達假設或猜測的詞語，但它們之間有些微的差異。 &amp;ldquo;Suppose&amp;rdquo; 基於已知或可接受的前提下提出一個假設，通常假設是基於事實或常識的推論。它可能有</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>appraise | evaluation</title>
      <link>https://chang-wen-chen.github.io/thesaurus/appraise_evaluation/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://chang-wen-chen.github.io/thesaurus/appraise_evaluation/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Evaluate&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;appraise&amp;rdquo; are two terms that involve assessing something, but they have slightly different connotations and applications. Evaluate: This term implies a comprehensive assessment or analysis of something, often with the aim of understanding its worth, quality, effectiveness, or significance. Evaluation typically involves considering various factors, gathering information, and making judgments or conclusions based on criteria. It&amp;rsquo;s a broader term that can be applied in various contexts, such as</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>maintain | uphold</title>
      <link>https://chang-wen-chen.github.io/thesaurus/maintain_uphold/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://chang-wen-chen.github.io/thesaurus/maintain_uphold/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Maintain&amp;rdquo; typically refers to the act of keeping something in a particular state or condition, often through regular efforts or actions. It can imply preserving, supporting, or caring for something over time. &amp;ldquo;Maintain&amp;rdquo; 通常指的是透過定期的努力或行動，將某物保持在特定的狀態或條件中。它可以暗示</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>commitment | promise</title>
      <link>https://chang-wen-chen.github.io/thesaurus/commitment_promise/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://chang-wen-chen.github.io/thesaurus/commitment_promise/</guid>
      <description>A commitment holds more weight than a simple promise Emphasis on intent: Commitment signifies a genuine desire to fulfill the promise, suggesting sincerity and motivation. Focus on strength: Commitment implies a stronger promise than one can readily deliver, highlighting its ambitious nature. Contrast with indulgence: Commitment stands against indulgence, emphasizing dedication and perseverance as key differentiators. In essence, commitments go beyond empty promises, demonstrating a willingness to put in the</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
